利奥，我们有一些问题要问你。
Leo, we have some questions for you.
Leo, tenemos unas preguntas para ti.
Leo，你会参加 2026 年世界杯吗？
Leo, are you going to play in the 2026 World Cup?
Leo, ¿vas a jugar en el Mundial 2026?
不。
No.
第一次。
First time.
Primera vez.
感谢您的时间和机会。
Thank you for your time and the opportunity.
Gracias por tu tiempo y la oportunidad.
谢谢。
Gracias.
你准备好了吗，弗雷迪？
Are you ready, Freddy?
¿Estás listo, Freddy?
开始了。
Here we go.
Aquí vamos.
我们从头开始，从欧洲赛场开始，直到来到美国职业足球大联盟。
We start from the beginning, from the European fields until we get here to the MLS.
Empezamos del principio, de los campos europeos hasta llegar aquí a la MLS.
是什么吸引你来到迈阿密国际队和美国踢球？
What attracted you to playing here for Inter Miami and in the United States?
¿Qué te atrajo de jugar aquí en el Inter Miami y en Estados Unidos?
事实是，俱乐部刚刚成立的那一刻，以及……
The truth is that the moment the club was just starting and the moment it was...
La verdad es que el momento que estaba el club recién iniciando y el momento que estaba...
我也在那里，我认为他们取得了很多成就来实现这一目标，现在它发生了。
I was there too, I think they achieved a lot of things to make it happen and now it happens.
Estaba yo también, creo que consiguieron muchísimas cosas para que se dé y ya dé.
帮助这种成长吸引了我。
helping that growth seduced me.
de ayudar a ese crecimiento me sedujo.
好吧，我很高兴 MLS 与其他比赛相比有何不同？
And well, I'm happy. How is MLS different compared to other competitions?
Y bueno, estoy feliz ¿En qué se diferencia la MLS comparada con otras competiciones?
有很多热情，我有点没有意识到，因为我知道这种热情......
There is a lot of passion, something that I was a little unaware of because I knew about the passion for...
Hay mucha pasión, cosa que por ahí desconocía un poco porque sabía de la pasión por...
篮球、棒球、美式足球、橄榄球那里少了一些，但让我很惊讶。
basketball, baseball, American football, football was a little less there, but it surprised me a lot.
basque, béisbol, fútbol americano, por ahí el fútbol era un poco menos, pero me sorprendió muchísimo.
这是一个竞争非常激烈的联赛，离开对整个球队来说都很困难，因为球队变得更强了。
It is a very competitive league where going away is difficult for the entire team because the team becomes stronger.
Es una liga muy competitiva donde ir de visitante a todo el equipo le cuesta porque el equipo se hace fuerte.
去美国任何地方，都能看到满座的体育场。
Going anywhere in the United States and seeing full stadiums.
El ir a cualquier parte de Estados Unidos y ver los estadios llenos.
非常喜欢他的球队。
very fan of his teams.
muy fanático de sus equipos.
我很惊讶，因为我不知道。
I was surprised because I didn't know.
Me sorprendió porque no conocía.
我喜欢它，我喜欢我所经历的。
I enjoy it and I like what I experienced.
Lo disfruto y me gusta lo que viví.
和？
And?
¿Y qué?
你有没有想过美国职业足球大联盟的天才球员们？
Do you think a little about the talents that are also here in MLS?
¿Opinas un poco de los talentos que también hay aquí en MLS?
他们为未来的人才投入了大量资金。
They are putting a lot into talents for the future.
Están metiendo mucho en los talentos para el futuro.
事实上，这对于年轻人来说是一个很好的机会，对于联盟来说也是一个很好的机会和时刻。
The truth is that it is a nice opportunity for young people, it is also a nice opportunity and a moment for the League to be next.
La verdad es que es una linda oportunidad para la gente joven, también es una linda oportunidad y un momento para que la Liga sea el siguiente.
可以帮助MLS和孩子们的成长。
and can help the growth of the MLS and the kids.
y puede ayudar al crecimiento de la MLS y de los chifos.
我认为所有这些都有帮助，让他们可以继续更多地出去。
And I think all this helps so they can continue going out even more.
Y creo que todo esto ayuda para que puedan seguir saliendo mucho más todavía.
快点！
Come on!
¡Vamos!
当你到达美国职业足球大联盟时，你的风格稍微改变了，带球少了一些，传球多了，对吗？
You changed your style a little when you arrived in the MLS, a little less dribbling and more passing, right?
¿Vos cambiaste un poco de estilo con el llegar al MLS, un poco menos de driblar y más de pasar, no?
我也按计划暂时改变了自己的风格。
I was also changing my style a little for the moment, by plan.
Fui cambiando un poco de estilo también por el momento, por plan.
我这个年纪，我正在适应一切，我正在重塑自己并适应联赛，这对我来说是
my age, I was adapting a little to everything, I was reinventing myself and adapting to the League as well, which for me was
mi edad, fui adaptando un poco a todo, me fui reinventando yo y adaptándome a la Liga también, que para mí era
它是新的，从一开始我就感觉很舒服。
It was new and I felt very comfortable from the beginning.
Era nuevo y me sentí muy cómodo desde el principio.
我想问你一些关于平衡的问题，对吗？
I wanted to ask you a little about balance, right?
Quería preguntarte un poco de balance, ¿no?
从这第一...
From this first...
De esta primera...
这是MLS的经验。
It's experience in MLS.
Es experiencia en MLS.
你来到这里是第一个完整的赛季，然后你参加了美洲杯。
You arrived the first full year, then you went through the Copa América.
Tú has llegado el primer año completo, luego pasaste por la Copa América.
我们立刻就明白了，一些挑战，一些胜利，现在季后赛即将到来，这是一个重要的时刻。
and it was immediately clear, some challenges, winning, now the playoffs are coming, it is an important moment.
y ya inmediatamente claro, algunos desafíos, ganando, ahora llegan los playoffs, es un momento importante.
您对 NM​​DS 迄今为止的历程有何看法？
What do you think of the journey so far at NMDS?
¿Qué opinas del camino hasta ahora en NMDS?
这一切都有点壮观，不是吗？
It was all a bit spectacular, wasn't it?
Fue todo un poco espectacular, ¿no?
因为我们到达并始终成为我们需要获胜的格拉诺俱乐部。
because we arrived and always to be the Grano Club we needed to win.
porque nosotros llegábamos y siempre para ser el Grano Club necesitábamos ganar.
冠军头衔竞争激烈，俱乐部在美国职业足球大联盟(MLS)中经历了糟糕的一年。
The title was competitive, the club was coming off a bad year in the MLS.
El título se competitivo, el club venía de un año malo en el MLS.
我到达后不久，我们就赢得了联赛杯，这是俱乐部的第一个冠军，这是一件非同寻常的事情。
and shortly after I arrived we won the League Cup, the first title for the club, which was something extraordinary.
y al poco tiempo de poder llegar yo conseguimos la League Cup, el primer título para el club, que fue algo extraordinario.
对于每个人来说，现在都怀着极大的愿望和许多愿望......
for everyone and now with great desire and many wishes to...
para todos y ahora con muchas ganas y muchas deseamos de...
能够面对这些季后赛，赢得美国职业足球大联盟并举起另一个冠军。
to be able to face these playoffs, win the MLS and lift another title.
de poder afrontar estos playoffs, ganar la MLS y levantar otro título.
在个人层面上，尤​​其是在俱乐部方面，他们为实现这一目标付出了巨大的努力。
on a personal level and above all to the club that did so much to make that happen.
a nivel personal y sobre todo al club que tanto hizo para que eso pase.
这支球队能走向何方？作为一名国际迈阿密球员，你希望在这支球队中实现什么目标？
Where can this team go and what goal would you like to achieve as an Inter Miami player with this team?
¿Dónde puede llegar este equipo y cuál objetivo te gustaría alcanzar como jugador del Inter Miami con este equipo?
克卢日没有设定限制...
Cluj does not set a limit for...
El Cluj no se pone límite por...
因为那是他们的哲学，永远想要……
because that is their philosophy, to always want...
porque esa es la filosofía de ellos, de querer siempre...
总是想要更多，他们所做的一切都证明了这一点，直到……
of always wanting more and it was demonstrated by everything they did until...
de querer siempre más y quedó demostrado por todo lo que hicieron hasta...
到目前为止，能够在美国职业足球大联盟（MLS）中继续成长并取得伟大成就，为什么不在……
so far and to be able to continue growing and to be great within the MLS and why not within...
hasta el momento y poder seguir creciendo y poder ser grande dentro de la MLS y por qué no dentro de...
在哪里？
Where?
¿Dónde?
在哪里？
Where?
¿Dónde?
现在我想问你一些关于即将发生的令人兴奋的事情。
Now I wanted to ask you a little about the excitement of what is coming.
Ahora quería preguntarte un poco por la emoción de lo que llega.
MLS季后赛是一个非常重要的时刻。
The MLS playoffs are a very important moment.
Los playoff de la MLS es un momento muy importante.
但第一个也是打破了赛季积分纪录。
but the first was also breaking the record for points in the season.
pero el primero ha sido romper también el récord de puntos en la temporada.
这对你来说非常特别。
This has been very special for you.
Esto ha sido muy especial para vosotros.
之后球队如何庆祝？
How did the team celebrate after that?
¿Cómo celebró el equipo después de eso?
我们很高兴并庆祝了这一成就，因为这是......
We were happy and celebrated the achievement, because it was something...
Nos pusimos felices y festejamos por el logro, porque era algo...
一些困难而重要的事情，但我们知道我们真正想要的标题是
something difficult and important, but we are aware that the real title we want is the
algo difícil e importante, pero somos conscientes de que el verdadero título que queremos es la
美国职业足球大联盟，我们将为之奋斗并专注于附加赛。
the MLS and that we are going to fight for it and be focused on the play-offs.
la MLS y que vamos a pelear por ello y estar mentalizados en los play-offs.
做出历史性成就的关键因素是什么？
What are going to be the key factors to do something historic?
¿Cuáles van a ser los factores clave para hacer algo histórico?
这一年里我们有很多...
During the year we had many...
Durante el año tuvimos muchos...
...许多我们可以避免的错误，因为很多时候它们是...
...many mistakes which we can avoid because many times they were...
...muchos errores los cuales podemos evitar porque muchas veces fueron...
至少可以说，非常愚蠢的错误......
Very stupid mistake, to say the least...
Error muy tonto, por decirlo de...
在某种程度上，在这些附加赛中他们无法超越我们，因为这可能会让你付出代价
in some way and that in these play-offs they cannot pass us because it could cost you
de alguna forma y que en estos play-offs no nos pueden pasar porque te puede costar la
......淘汰，然后我们必须变得更加强大......并利用我们获得的优势。”
...elimination and then we have to be even stronger... ...and take advantage of that advantage we got."
...de eliminación y después tenemos que ser aún más fuertes... ...y aprovechar esa ventaja que conseguimos".
您如何看待迈阿密国际赢得 MSS 杯的机会？
How do you see Inter Miami's chances of winning the MSS Cup?
¿Cómo ves las chances del Inter Miami de ganar la MSS Cup?
我认为我们是最受欢迎的球队之一，但我认为也会有一些强队
I think we are one of the favorites, but I think there are also tough teams that are going to be
Creo que somos uno de los favoritos, pero creo que también hay equipos duros que van a ser
非常难对付的对手，他们不会向我们透露任何信息，但我认为其他球队也尊重我们，就像他们尊重我们一样。
very difficult rivals and they are not going to reveal anything to us, but I think the other teams also respect us as they respect us.
rivales muy difíciles y que no nos van a revelar nada, pero creo que los demás equipos también nos respetan a nosotros como a nosotros ellos.
再见，朋友们！
Goodbye, friends!
¡Adiós, amigos!
我们风格的一些快速 4-3-3 问题。
Some quick 4-3-3 questions in our style.
Unas preguntas rápidas de 4-3-3 en nuestro estilo.
你什么时候在家带孩子？
When are you at home with your children?
¿Cuándo estás en casa con tus hijos?
他玩的是什么游戏啊！
What a game he plays!
¡Qué juego juega!
球！
The ball!
¡La pelota!
所有足球总是涉及一些小比赛、一些触球、一些传球。
All football always involves a little game, some touches, some passes.
Todo el fútbol siempre pasa por algún partidito, algunos toques, algunos pases.
我有时会玩，但通常...
I play it sometimes, but usually...
La play a veces, pero generalmente...
当你再次打球时你给他建议，你说什么？
And you give him advice when you play with the ball again, what do you say?
Y le das consejos cuando vuelves a jugar con la pelota, ¿qué le decís?
这取决于时刻，取决于...
It depends on the moment, it depends...
Depende del momento, depende...
三者中的哪一个也是如此，因为其中一个比另一个更热。
to which of the three too, because one is hotter than the other.
a cual de los tres también, porque alguno es más calentón que otro.
是的，但我和他一起打球，这也给了我......
Yes, but I play with him and that also gives me...
Sí, pero juego con él y también eso me da...
他们给我建议，当他们分享时也批评我。
They give me advice, they criticize me too when they come to share.
Me dan consejos, me critican a mí también cuando ven a compartir.
除了足球之外，您还喜欢练习哪些运动？
What other sports do you like to practice outside of football?
¿Qué otros deportes te gusta practicar afuera del fútbol?
我喜欢板网球，我喜欢...
I like paddle tennis, I like it...
Me gusta el padel, me gusta...
篮球、网球，但我很喜欢练习。
Basketball, tennis, but I really like practicing.
El basque, tenis, pero practicar me gusta mucho.
你在球场上经历了很多标志性时刻。
You've had so many iconic moments on the court.
Has tenido muchísimos momentos icónicos en la cancha.
除此之外还有一些我们不知道的有趣的事情。
outside of it something fun that we don't know.
afuera de ella algo divertido que no conocemos.
与人相处的事情很多，人们做了很多...
So many things with people, people do so much...
Tantas cosas con la gente, la gente hace tanta...
有时如此疯狂，以至于你无法相信。
So much madness sometimes that you can't believe it.
Tanta locura a veces que no se puede creer.
我来自阿根廷，那里的人非常...
I am from Argentina, the people are very...
Yo soy de Argentina, que la gente es muy...
热情、外向、有能力
passionate, demonstrative and capable of
apasionada, demostrativa y que es capaz de
做任何事情，问候你，拍照，靠近。
to do anything, to greet you, for a photo, to be close.
de hacer cualquier cosa, por saludarte, por una foto, por estar cerca.
意大利也一样，一切都相似
well in Italy too, everything similar
bueno en Italia también, todo parecido
所以我不记得了，但事实是我经历了很多疯狂。
So I don't remember, but the truth is that I went through a lot of madness.
Así que no me acuerdo, pero la verdad es que pasé por mucha locura.
比赛前你有什么特别的放松习惯吗？
Do you have a special routine to relax before a game?
¿Tienes alguna rutina especial para relajarte antes de un partido?
喝点伙计，这取决于比赛的时间，但没什么，我想。
drink mate, it depends on the time of the game, but nothing, I thought.
tomar mate, depende de la hora del partido, pero nada, pesé.
当谈到食物时，你会感到内疚。
Your guilty pleasure when it comes to food.
Tu placer culposo cuando se trata de comida.
冰淇淋。
The ice cream.
El helado.
事实是……
The truth is that...
La verdad que...
我不太喜欢食物，但我很喜欢甜点。
I'm not so much into food, but I am into desserts.
No soy tanto de comida, pero sí de los postres.
我们知道您是动作玩偶的粉丝，对吧？
We know you're a fan of action figures, right?
Sabemos que sos fan de los muñecos de acción, ¿no?
属于超级英雄。
Of superheroes.
De superhéroes.
如果有梅西这样的人，他会拥有怎样的超能力。
If there was one of Leo Messi, what superpower he would have.
Si hubiera uno de Leo Messi, qué superpoder tendría.
一个博物馆。
A museum.
Un museo.
狮子博物馆。
A lion museum.
Un museo león.
或者飞翔，但没有音乐。
Or fly, but there is no music.
O volar, pero no hay music.
我们来谈谈国家队、世界杯等等。
Let's talk a little about the national team, the World Cup, about all that.
Vamos a hablar un poco de la selección, del Mundial, de todo eso.
你准备好了吗？
Are you ready?
¿Estás listo?
Leo，你会参加 2026 年美国世界杯吗？
Leo, are you going to play in the 2026 World Cup in the United States?
Leo, ¿vas a jugar al Mundial 2026 de Estados Unidos?
我知道，事实是他们问过我很多次，尤其是......
I know, the truth is that they asked me a lot of times, especially...
Yo lo sé, la verdad es que me lo preguntaron un montón de veces, sobre todo...
在阿根廷，我希望今年能够取得好成绩，我希望能够开始。
in Argentina and I hope to finish well this year, I hope to start.
en Argentina y espero terminar bien este año, espero empezar.
这一年是非常好的季前赛，去年我没有参加过所有的旅行……
A year being a very good preseason, which I didn't have last year with all the trips that...
Un año siendo una muy buena pretemporada, la cual no la tuve el año pasado con todos los viajes que...
我们拥有却一无所有，从那里开始，看看我的感觉如何，很好。
that we had and nothing, from there, seeing how I feel and good.
que tuvimos y nada, a partir de ahí, viendo cómo me siento y bien.
我知道我们同时很接近。
I know we are close at the same time.
Sé que estamos cerquita al mismo tiempo.
已经过去很长一段时间了，足球界发生了很多事情，所以......
It's a long time and a lot of things happen in football so...
es mucho tiempo y en el fútbol pasan muchísimas cosas así que...
我不认为，只是生活...
that I don't think, just live the...
que no pienso, simplemente vivir el...
日复一日，不去思考其他事情。
The day to day without thinking beyond.
El día a día sin pensar más allá.
您职业生涯的下一步是什么？
What is the next step in your career?
¿Cuál es el próximo paso de tu carrera?
成为一名教练还是其他什么？
Be a coach or something different?
¿Ser entrenador o algo diferente?
我不知道，我真的不知道。
I don't know, I really don't know.
No lo sé, la verdad que no lo sé.
我知道我不喜欢哪位教练。
I know which coach I think I wouldn't like.
Sé que entrenador creo que no me gustaría.
我不想成为这样的人，但我真的不确定自己能成为什么。
I wouldn't like to be, but I'm not sure what I can be, really.
No me gustaría ser, pero tampoco tengo claro qué es lo que puedo llegar a ser, la verdad.
我更看重一切。
I value everything that is much more.
Valoro muchísimo más todo lo que es.
我每天的生活都是我以前做过的，所以我只想着玩耍……
What I live on a day-to-day basis, that I did before, so I only think about playing and...
Lo que vivo en el día a día, que antes por ahí, así que pienso solo en jugar y en...
训练并度过一生。
Train and get through life.
Entrenar y pasar la vida.
Leo，最后一个问题是我想给你看一些东西。
Leo, the last question is I want to show you something.
Leo, la última pregunta es quiero mostrarte algo.
您希望我们如何记住您？
How do you want us to remember you?
¿Cómo quieres que te vamos a recordar?
喜欢家里的孩子吗？
Like the kid of the family?
¿Cómo el pibe de la familia?
当然，永远和家人在一起。
Of course, always with your family.
Claro, con tu familia siempre.
就像饥饿的梅西一样，他赢得了一切，但总是渴望赢得更多。
like the hungry Leo Messi who won everything but is always hungry to win more.
como el Leo Messi con hambre que ganó todo pero sigue siempre con hambre de ganar más.
或者是征服世界的 Eumessi、Pibre del Rosario。
or the Eumessi, the Pibre del Rosario who conquered the world.
o el Eumessi, el Pibre del Rosario que conquistó el mundo.
这三者你更喜欢哪一个？
Which of the three do you prefer?
¿Cuál de las tres prefieres?
事实是，人们随心所欲地记住我。
The truth is that people remember me however they want.
La verdad es que la gente me recuerde como quiera.
我很感激。
I am grateful.
Yo soy un agradecido.
他的职业生涯以及所取得的成就。
of the career he had and of having been able to achieve.
de la carrera que tuvo y de haber podido conseguir.
我在那里取得的一切成就让我很幸运能够实现最伟大的梦想。
Everything I achieved there I was lucky to achieve the greatest dream that was.
Todo lo que conseguí hacia allá tuve la suerte de conseguir el mayor sueño que era.
赢得世界杯，我付出了如此多的努力，付出了如此多的代价，我很幸运......
win the World Cup, which I struggled so much and cost so much, I was lucky enough to...
ganar el Mundial, que tanto me lié y tanto costó, tuve la suerte de...
与巴塞罗那一起赢得一切，与国家队一起，拥有美好的生活和美好的家庭。
to win everything with Barcelona, ​​with the national team, have a life and a beautiful family.
de ganar todo con el Barcelona, con la selección, tener una vida y una familia hermosa.
我感谢上帝让我感动的一切，人们记得我……
that I am grateful to God for everything that has touched me and that people remember me as...
que soy un agradecido a Dios por todo lo que me tocó y que la gente me recuerde como...
你有最喜欢的吗？
Do you have a favorite?
¿Tienes una favorita?
您最喜欢的图形？
A graphic that you like the most?
¿Una gráfica que te gusta más?
是的，家人，永远是家人。
Yes, the family, always the family.
Sí, la familia, siempre la familia.
来吧，我们签一下这个。
Come on, let's sign this one.
Vamos, firmamos esta.
我们就是这样。
We do like this.
Hacemos así.
如果你不能签字...
If you can't sign it...
Si no se la puede firmar...
不，谢谢。
No, thanks.
No, gracias.
谢谢 Neu 接受采访。
Thanks, Neu, for the interview.
Gracias, Neu, por la entrevista.
这是一种乐趣。
It has been a pleasure.
Ha sido un placer.
谢谢。
Gracias.